Hey everyone, this is a quick demo of Vichar
and its enterprise features. So,
after signing up, you'll see this dashboard. You can top up any amount of
credits and then spend these credits on any
of these models listed here. If you want to bring your own keys,
if you have credits on an account,
you can do this here.
You have the activity page where you can see the exact breakdown of every
single request, how much money we saved you in terms of,
uh, in case of a promotion that we have ongoing right now.
You can see the routing decisions, so you can always choose if you want
a specific price to log in or a specific provider.
By default, we choose the best route for you with our routing algorithm.
You can see the breakdown of agents.
We support all the coding agents that are out there,
so you can use any model with any of these. You can see the
breakdown by model, by API key.
In the enterprise level, we also breakdown of the whole organizations and users.
I'll show that in a second. For full insights,
you can also drill down by API key,
if you need, and see the exact spend.
Let's see the spend here. Cost. Yep. Uh,
you have a bunch more stuff. The API keys page allows
you to provision API keys and send it either to your team, or you
can give it to specific, uh, agents. All of the API
keys can have specific restrictions.
In terms of expiration, usage limits,
and specifically also rules,
so that you can only allow specific models or providers,
or pricing constraints, IP ranges in the enterprise offering,
so you can restrict however you want in
the end. Let's see,
we have some caching, we can save you some costs in terms of identical
LLM requests, the provider tokens caching is always enabled,
of course. We have the team management here,
let's switch to our enterprise organization for this real quick,
so, we have the team here,
you can invite All right. People set the specific role,
uhm, give them access to specific projects,
we have a compliance page where you can customize your
compliance, uhm,
yeah, requirements, so you can choose specific ones,
maybe let's say we only want to route to US companies,
and you will see here. what providers are eligible.
We have, uh, also custom providers and custom models,
which, uh, you will also, which you will also see in the model catalog
once you edit, this is all available in the enterprise plan.
We also have guardrails,
so you can block specific actions.
For some, we also have RedactN1,
so, for example, for personal, personal information,
in case it's detected, it can be redacted,
and then it will show up in the security events page here.
This helps you just to prevent leaking of internal company information,
uhm,
or outright block it. Thank you.
And this is also something we continuously improve and push updates on.
We have organization-wide analytics,
so you can see the spend by user.
Let me switch to an organization real quick,
because this one is configured with SSO.
So, we have this SSO page here. This is already configured. You can configure
this with Microsoft Entra or Okta or whatever SSO tool
that you use. We also have SCIM, so it will automatically sync from your
SSO provider. So here the team is synced.
You can add some default spend limits.
so you can see developers can spend a lot more money.
More than $200 a month on them. You can still override it for specific
users specifically.
So that will take precedence. You can also manage for specific users,
what models or providers they can or cannot use.
The analytics, uh, page allows
you to see organizations. So you can break
down by project, you can break down by user,
see the spend over time or in total.
Of course, you can break this down for whatever time duration that you need.
And so this is an admin or owner.
So this has, this user has access to all of the things.
We have master keys as well,
so that you can program it, programmatically export statistics.
You can manage API key permissions, provision API keys,
revoke API keys, roll API keys and all of that stuff.
And then for a specific user,
this is how it would look. So we have the login page
here, right? then you would. Login with SSO,
as a developer, and then you sign in,
you see it goes to Microsoft Entra.
In this case, I'm already logged in. And the user,
this user is a developer, so they have only insights into their own usage.
So on the dashboard, they see their own usage only,
they can self-provision their API keys,
So they have the same mechanism.
In this case, they want to create different API keys for different agents or
on the cloud.
Of course, it will inherit the limits that are set on the organization And
this will also have the model catalog that they can choose
from. Here is, of course, whatever the organization policy sets.
So, for example, the. This one is, uh, not, uh,
available under the current company's settings.
Yeah.